# Mahmoud Ramadan Abbas

React & JavaScript developer.

€ 01024759842♥ Minya-Egypt■ mahmoudrabass11@gmail.com

#### About me.

I am a javascript developer who is very interested in the web. I have experience in designing responsive websites with Html & Css, Js and Reactjs and have knowledge about the back-end and dealing with the APIs besides I have built some project with nodejs, express, mongodb/mysql and Reactj (MERN stack).

### **SKILLS**

· Designing responsive websites

Problem solving

Arabic English



Software: Vscode, Excel, Word,

PowerPoint, Illustrator.

#### **EDUCATION**

2018 - 2022 Minya, Egypt **Bachelor degree in Information Systems** 

Faculty of computers and information

Minya university.

## **EXPERIENCE**

2021 - 2021

Minya, Egypt

2022 - 2022

Minya, Egypt

Computer vision training

ITI institute

**MERAN** stack training

ITI institute

May. 2022 – Jun. 2022

Minya, Egypt

**Graduation Project** 

Website to help the painters to display their works and sell them in (MERN).

- I managed the state with react-redux in client side.
- I built the data store of the whole application and handled the api.
- I built some apis in the server side.

#### **INTERESTS**

✓ Sports : Swimming and Football.

**GitHub**: github.com/mahmoudrabbas

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/mahmoud-r-abbas-1b3a1116a